this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this site can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
luffy was sent flying from the sabo di archipelago by bartholomew kuma after soaring through the sky
for hours he found himself in a kingdom inhabited entirely by women its name was amazon lily
don't let him escape there she is perfect luffy captured a kuja warrior by the name of margaret
and fled their village but could not escape the island if this keeps up much longer i'll end up
growing attached to you hold on just stop i am vice admiral mamunga of navy headquarters
warlord of the sea and pirate empress boa hancock i have come for you reveal yourself
i already told you i like being a warlord however i loathe the world government
i have no interest in following their orders surely i can find a better solution
love love be unless you reappear in two days your position will be revoked
do as you wish
the secret hidden on the backs luffy and the snake princess meet
open the gate
the snake princess has returned
we missed you
welcome home puja pirates we're glad you're back
welcome home
we love you
thankimas
parable
we loved you
look good wrong
yes daisy
we brought back lots of loops
they're so awesome
i'd better join the pirates when i grow up
it's the gorgon sisters
oh
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
Welcome home, Daisy!
Hi! Daisy!
Hey, Wingo!
Blue bed!
Hello!
Welcome home, Marigold!
Hey, Sandersonia!
They're really worked up.
They simply missed our dear sister.
It was a lengthy journey.
Can you blame them?
She smiled at me!
She was smiling at me!
Welcome back, Princess.
We've prepared a monkey carriage for you.
Is there anything to report?
No. Everything's fine.
Gently now. It's quite fragile. Carry it slowly.
Iron ore, gunpowder, alcohol, and northern crops.
What a truly impressive haul.
Yeah, we plundered a couple of merchant vessels in one pirate ship.
Not to mention the loads of cargo we claimed from a central government ship.
You Kucha pirates really are a force to be reckoned with.
Guess so.
Are you handling the snake princess's gift?
Oh, yeah, don't worry.
It's on the way to the castle now.
Ron, did you collect any books?
Down here.
Granny Nyon!
Books, huh?
Oh, we did appropriate a recent newspaper off the central government ship.
Here. All yours.
Oh, my goodness!
Welcome back, Snake Princess!
We're so glad to have you home, Snake Princess.
Me too. It's nice to be back.
I thought you might want to enjoy your spoils of war,
so I've polished the most exquisite jewel from the batch for you.
Oh?
Oh, wow! No jewel in the world can compare to her smile!
But Snake Princess!
A gaudy rock like that would be an unsightly blemish upon my beauty.
Inishida, what is this?
Oh, I forgot.
The children of the village lovingly crafted a statue of your likeness out of clay as a gift.
It's endearing how much love and labor they poured into its creation.
Well...
We made this to show the Snake Princess how much we love her.
It took them forever to bring it up to the castle because it would break if they dropped it.
Don't you think it's cute?
It's me.
But made out of mud.
Snake Princess!
Don't bring such filth into the castle.
It's inelegant.
Throw it away at once and clean the floor.
I'm curious, Inishida.
Oh?
About?
I couldn't help but notice the city defenders were absent from the wharf upon our arrival.
Uh...
Actually...
You see...
A ferocious and violent monkey came rampaging out of the jungle.
The size and brute strength of the beast was simply astonishing.
So everyone has left for the jungle to hunt it.
I see.
Let's go.
Let's get into the petty crisis.
There he is.
Take this!
Has the beast met his end?
Look!
He's over there!
Ah!
Are all men as stubborn as this one?
Do not think you can escape your death.
It's no concern. They'll be back shortly.
I'm truly sorry they weren't there to greet you.
No matter.
Well then, would you care for a drink?
White sake.
Go ahead and make that two while you're at it.
Granny Mion.
How nice of you to defile my private chambers.
I didn't see you come in.
How did you get in here?
Forget how I'm here.
Get rid of her.
Hold on. Listen, snake princess.
You forgot, please.
Now say it.
Please listen, snake princess.
I have just learned that there's a ship from Central anchored off our shores.
They've come here with the express purpose of summoning you, have they, Nyut?
The Central Government has ordered you into active duty.
That's right. They want me to go to war.
Why are you here? You must go.
You must uphold the agreement or they'll revoke your title.
I know you've just returned, but surely you still have the strength to fight.
I do.
But I'm afraid to go.
Oh, she's like a weird old puppy.
Wait!
I'm not funny for that.
Nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut, nyut.
Now, think this through, all that is truly protecting our nation is your title as warlord.
Our greatest deterrence from outside forces is Amazon Lily's location,
here in the Sea King riddled waters of the Calm Belt.
But as time marches forward, so does technology.
And now these central dwellers have ships that provide them with safe passage through these parts.
We need a new weapon to keep them at bay.
Your rank as warlord is the sole reason they avoid our shores, despite the activities of the Kuja pirates.
Think of your people. Our island is home to helpless children and elderly.
If you lost your title, Amazon Lily would just be another nation of pirates,
and the government would bring ruin to us.
Now you're the one who sounds like she's afraid.
I am old. I could drop dead at any moment.
Gaze into this crystal ball and see your future.
Oh my. Her crystal ball is always right about the future.
It's never wrong about anything.
I shall conjure an image of your fate.
Your fortune!
Huh?
You idiot!
Throw her out!
Right now!
Yes, of course, Snake Princess!
Wait! Hear me out!
That's so rough!
I listen respectfully, and you treat me like a fool.
Did you think I'd fall for your chicanery?
Your reign here ended well over three generations ago.
How dare you act like you're still the empress of Amazon Lily?
Gloriosa.
It doesn't matter what I do.
I could lay waste to every inch of this nation of ours.
On a whim.
And still,
I would be forgiven because I'm beautiful.
Amazing!
She looks down on people so much that she looks up!
Why on earth should I listen to the words of a disgraced ruler
who abandoned her people to journey the outer seas?
Traitor to the Kuja!
So I live alone in penance on the outskirts of town!
Which is where you should be at this very moment.
Do not presume to tell me what to do!
I'm the reigning empress!
Snake Princess!
Put me down already!
That said,
I can't help but admire your overwhelming passion.
You may be right.
You agreed to my request?
Thank you for understanding the needs of your people!
How wonderful!
So,
how soon will you be leaving?
Never know your place, fool!
No!
Now get out of my sight!
A curse on you, Snake Princess!
Yeah!
Snake Princess,
you threw an old woman out the window!
What an accident!
Oh, of course!
We know it wasn't your fault!
Now clean up all this broken glass.
Yes, ma'am!
That irritating old hag!
Granny Neon?
I may be old,
but I'm still a Kuja warrior!
My skills haven't withered a bit!
I touched her.
Have you prepared my bathwater yet?
Yes!
I'll issue the advisory immediately!
Your attention, please!
The Snake Princess will now bathe!
Now, stay still!
I'm almost done!
Well, sorry!
Huh?
We must evacuate the castle now!
Hey, come on!
We've got to go!
But I just sat down!
I'm still eating!
Come on!
Hurry, everyone!
If you're on duty today,
report to your post!
Sounds like it's bath time!
Get ready, girls!
They're clearing out the castle now!
It's about to get packed in here!
For the next several hours,
no one is allowed to enter the castle
under any circumstances!
What are you doing here?
You know you're not allowed
past the barrier, right?
Yeah, but why is it such a big deal
when the universe takes a bath?
Everyone acts like we're going
to war or something!
First things first,
how old are you?
Eight years old.
Well, then I think I can tell you.
Wait, you don't mean
the secret.
That's right.
You're in charge of keeping watch.
As you wish, dear sister.
Take your time.
You see, the Gorgon was a monster.
It stalked the tides
of the central oceans.
If anyone made the mistake
of gazing upon this horrifying creature,
they would be turned to stone.
After facing countless perils
along a treacherous journey,
the snake princess and her sisters
encountered the monster
and managed to slay it.
But the screams of the dying abomination
were laced with evil,
and it placed the sisters under a curse.
The penetrating eyes of the monster
were etched across the flesh
of the sisters' backs.
So they remain forever staring,
even today.
And if anyone gazes upon these wicked eyes,
their body will harden into stone
and they'll die.
That's why the Gorgon sisters
refuse to remove their clothing
before another human.
As a matter of precaution,
they always post guards
when they bathe,
and they secure and evacuate the castle.
Now listen to that
and they always turn away
in this case.
Sounds like the man's over there.
The snakes must have found him.
Stop! Get off me!
Did you see where he went?
Yeah, he ran up the side of the mountain.
You don't think he could be headed back to the village, do you?
I thought he was bound and determined to find a ship.
What?
There we go.
Ah, geez, that really sucked.
Okay, now what's next?
They'll come and shoot me with arrows if I just sit here.
Wait a sec.
Margaret did say they've got a pirate ship.
I wonder how hard it'd be to borrow it.
That won't work.
Nami's not here.
I'd get lost in no time without her.
I got it.
All I gotta do is ask someone for a ride in their ship.
Wherever they're going, I'm sure they won't mind a quick trip to Sabaody.
So, who am I gonna ask for a ride?
Probably gotta be someone important and high up.
And if they're high up, that means they gotta live in a tall building, right?
My head's on fire from all this thinking.
Right.
Guess I'll just try the first tall building I can find.
Let's see.
That one'll do.
We need to hurry.
By this point, the snake princess has probably returned.
We'll be in trouble if she finds the man.
You suck roof!
What was that?
The roof of the castle tower collapsed.
Oh no.
This is bad.
That's where the empress is taking a bath!
I can't breathe! I'm trapped!
I'm already dead!
It's real shallow!
I'm safe!
This is... a huge bath!
Huh?
Oh man...
Hey!
That thing on your back...
Huh?
It looks...
Kinda familiar...
You saw it?
Luffy is captured once more after seeing the snake princess's secret.
Margaret and her friends try to defend him, but Hancock is unmoved and turns them all to stone.
Luffy's angry to see the Empress petrify her own comrades, but is powerless to help as he faces his own execution.
On the next Wood Beast, Heartless Judgment, Margaret is turned to stone.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!